http://www.thespectrum.net/privacy/

9/12/2019 ·
It's been a while since I updated. That revamped site hasn't really come to fruition yet. I've decided to dabble in some video game streaming which you can find on the homepage so hope you check out some of my latest videos and subscribe if you enjoy them :)
User Comments +
Msg Board / Sites +
Our Sites
· Manga Lyght
Friend Sites
· Chris Koehler
· Hitokiris Anonymous
Free E-mail +
Tired of having the same e-mail domain as everyone else? Add some character to your e-mail address by
signing up for you@fusiongt.com
It's completely free and offers you everything you need. Have the ability to check your e-mail address anywhere there's an Internet connection. Also, because you aren't
under one of the major companies, you won't be harassed by spam!
Click here to sign up!
Existing members login here
Username
Password
Spectrum Nexus Privacy Policy
You can feel confident about how we use the information you give us.
We will not disclose your information to any third parties. We will only use your information to help us provide services to you.
By using Spectrum Nexus' web site you accept our policy.
Do I have to give Spectrum Nexus personal information?
The only instances you will be asked to submit personal information is if you're sending us an e-mail through our
contact form, if you join the message forums, if you sign up for the free giveaway/newsletter,
or if you sign up for our free e-mail service.
Our newsletter is a service provided by FeedBlitz. They are a reputable company that provides free newsletter services to thousands of websites. By signing up for our newsletter you are accepting FeedBlitz's Privacy Policy.
Our free
e-mail service is provided to us by
Everyone.net. They are a reputable company that provides free e-mail service to
large businesses as well as colleges. We do not receive personal information when users sign up for
this e-mail service; we are only allowed to view user names (and not passwords). By signing up for this free e-mail service you are
accepting Everyone.net's Privacy Policy.
What does Spectrum Nexus do with my information?
If you submit an e-mail to us through our contact form we will only use that information to
send you a reply to your inquiry. If you sign up for the message forum
we will never use your personal information in a harmful way; nor will we share it with any third parties. Our free giveaway requires users to sign up for a newsletter, and we will send our newsletter to the email you provide. If you win the giveaway, we will require a name and address for us to ship the giveaway to you.
What about advertisements on Spectrum Nexus?
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
What about Spectrum Nexus' server logs, user rating scripts, and polls?
The only information that is stored is your IP address. This information will not be used in any other way beside
providing us with information such as if the user submitted a score through the user rating script they will not be permitted again to
submit it until after a certain amount of days. The same goes with server logs and polls; IP addresses are
simply used to enable our "user submitted information" to be more accurate (to discourage
malicious use of our system).
Links to other websites
We only link to websites that we feel will benefit the user.
Who should I contact?
If you have any concerns about the information we hold about you,
or the way we use it, please use our contact form to
send an e-mail to Spectrum Nexus.
For General Off-Topic ChatSN Chat Room
Spectrum Nexus Discord Chat Open 24/7
English scanlation spoilers allowed but put an ALERT!
User Comments | Post
Before posting, please follow the rules in this link.
The new Disqus is here so please set your "Discussion" to "Newest".
What rules?
Browse Manga:
Btooom!
Happy!
Skip Beat!
UQ Holder!
